<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LTI Launch Data :: LTI Toolkit</title>
    <link>https://alt.cs.ksu.edu/lti-toolkit/02-lti/03-launchdata/index.html</link>
    <description>The LTI Toolkit constructs a launchData object from each incoming LTI launch that contains the following information. Each attribute is documented with the original source of that attribute from both an LTI 1.0 and LTI 1.3 launch request. To simplify things, the baseURL and agsURL in the descriptions below have been replaced with variables that carry these values:&#xA;baseURL = &#34;https://purl.imsglobal.org/spec/lti/claim/&#34; agsURL = &#34;https://purl.imsglobal.org/spec/lti-ags/claim/&#34; LTI Launch Data Object launch_type - the type of LTI launch LTI 1.0: &#34;lti1.0&#34; LTI 1.3: &#34;lti1.3&#34; tool_consumer_key - the locally-generated key used to identify the tool consumer (either the OAuth Key for LTI 1.0 or the provided Key in the Login URL for LTI 1.3) LTI 1.0: thisisasupersecretkey LTI 1.3: thisisasupersecretkey course_id - the unique ID of the course LTI 1.0: context_id LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;context&#34;].id course_label - the short title of the course (e.g. &#34;CIS 101&#34;) LTI 1.0: context_label LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;context&#34;].label course_name - the full title of the course (e.g &#34;Computer Programming&#34;) LTI 1.0: context_title LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;context&#34;].title assignment_id - the unique ID of the assignment LTI 1.0: resource_link_id LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;lti1p1&#34;].resource_link_id assignment_lti_id - the unique LTI ID of the assignment LTI 1.0: ext_lti_assignment_id LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;resource_link&#34;].id assignment_name - the name of the assignment (e.g. &#34;Programming Lab 1&#34;) LTI 1.0: resource_link_title LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;resource_link&#34;].title return_url - the URL to return students to after finishing the assignment LTI 1.0: launch_presentation_return_url LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;launch_presentation&#34;].return_url outcome_url - the URL to submit grades to LTI 1.0: lis_outcome_service_url LTI 1.3: [agsUrl + &#34;endpoint&#34;].lineitem outcome_id - the ID of the outcome to submit (only present on student launches) LTI 1.0: lis_result_sourcedid LTI 1.3: null outcome_ags - information for the LTI Assignment &amp; Grade Services (AGS) LTI 1.0: null LTI 1.3: launchResult[agsUrl + &#34;endpoint&#34;] user_lis_id - the unique ID of the student for LTI 1.0 LTI 1.0: user_id LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;lti1p1&#34;].user_id user_lis13_id - the unique ID of the student for LTI 1.3 LTI 1.0: null LTI 1.3: launchResult.sub user_email - the email address of the student LTI 1.0: lis_person_contact_email_primary LTI 1.3: email May be omitted depending on privacy level selected user_name - the full name of the student (e.g. &#34;Willie Wildcat&#34;) LTI 1.0: lis_person_name_full LTI 1.3: name May be omitted depending on privacy level selected user_given_name - the given name (first name) of the student (e.g. &#34;Willie&#34;) LTI 1.0: lis_person_name_given LTI 1.3: given_name May be omitted depending on privacy level selected user_family_name - the famly name (last name or surname) of the student (e.g. &#34;Wildcat&#34;) LTI 1.0: lis_person_name_family LTI 1.3: family_name May be omitted depending on privacy level selected user_image - the URL of the profile image of the user LTI 1.0: user_image LTI 1.3: picture May be omitted depending on privacy level selected user_roles - the roles assigned to the user LTI 1.0: role LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;roles&#34;] custom - any custom parameters provided to the system (in LTI 1.0, they MUST be prefixed with lpp to be detected) LTI 1.0: search for any attributes prefixed with custom_ LTI 1.3: [baseUrl + &#34;custom&#34;] Four additional items are stored in the consumer database by the library itself, but aren’t passed to the user’s handleLaunch function:</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://alt.cs.ksu.edu/lti-toolkit/02-lti/03-launchdata/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>